# Levan Chincharauli

(+995) 568 692-916 levannchincharauli@gmail.com <u>FreeCodeCamp</u> <u>Codecademy</u> <u>Linkedin</u> <u>GitHub</u>

## **SUMMARY**

Motivated web development enthusiast with beginner experience in HTML/CSS/JS. Currently studying web fundamentals at <a href="freeCodeCamp.org">freeCodeCamp.org</a>; In close relationship with maths and numbers since school, with good understanding of stock market/investing/investing psychology. Excellent learner of new things.

### **SKILLS**

HTML, CSS, JavaScript

### **PROJECTS**

**Technical Documentation** 

**Landing Page** 

Survey Form

**Tribute Page** 

Random Quote Machine

GitHub User Search

### **EXPERIENCE**

09.2014 - PRESENT

LTD Chirina - Operator/translator

06.2014 - 08.2014

**Gpi Holding - Operator** 

07.2012 - 04.2014

Caucasus trader - Lecturer

### **EDUCATION**

09.2007 - 07.2013

Tbilisi State University - Master of business administration